hyperboards.com 2016-03-06

# Privacy Policy - Free Forums - Hyperboards

Last revision: March 8, 2012

Hyperboards is committed to fair information practices and privacy protection. Our Privacy Policy applies to all products, services, and web sites offered by Hyperboards. Information you share helps us improve our services, and our goal is to explain, as clearly as possible, what we do with information and how you can protect your privacy. If you have any questions about our Privacy Policy, please feel free to contact us through our website.

Our Privacy Policy explains:

  * What information we collect and why
  * How we use collected information
  * Your privacy options

## Information we collect

**Information we ask for** \- When you create or update your account, we may ask you for "personally identifying" information, such as your email address, date of birth, and gender. Any personal information we require is automatically hidden from public view and can be made public if you choose. If you purchase our products or services, you may also be asked for your address, phone number, credit card information, or other information that can be used to contact you or personally identify you.

**Cookies** \- When you visit Hyperboards, we transfer and store a small data file on your computer that helps us recognize you each time you visit, allowing us to keep you logged in, measure traffic to our site, and to track how you interact with our site so we can personalize your experience. Our advertisers may also utilize cookies, and their use of the information stored on those cookies is subject to their own privacy policies.

**Anonymous information** \- When you visit Hyperboards using a site-viewing client, such as a browser, we collect standard log information, such as your IP address, browser type, browser language, the type of request you made, and the date/time of the request.

This site is not intended for the use of children. Hyperboards does not solicit or knowingly collect information from children under 13 years old, and will not accept registration from them.

## How we use information we collect

We use personally identifying information that you provide to communicate with you, process transactions, customize advertising, personalize your experience, and conduct research for internal use to improve upon our products and services.

We may also use non-personally identifying information to analyze how people are using our site and its products and services. For example, using anonymous analytical data, we can see which forums get the most hits, what topics are the most popular, and using your IP address, we can determine your general location and better target advertising to users.

## Information sharing

Hyperboards will not share your personal information with other companies or individuals, except in the following situations:

  * **In relation to products or services** \- We disclose personal information to third parties in order to improve our products, services, and advertising. For example, we share information with companies that help us process information, deliver products to you, provide customer service, serve ads, and conduct customer satisfaction surveys. Your information will not be sold or shared with third parties for their marketing purposes.

  * **If we have your consent** \- We may at certain times present you with an opportunity to co-register with companies that provide special offers, products, and services of their own. Under no obligation, you may choose to opt-in and co-register with a third party, at which point we will share your personal information with them. Third party companies may have their own terms and policies that you are asked to agree to, and Hyperboards is not responsible for said third party terms, policies, or actions.

  * **As is required by law** \- We will share information if we are required to by law, or if we have a good faith belief that doing so is necessary in order to (a) conform to applicable law, regulation, legal process or enforceable governmental request, (b) enforce applicable Terms of Service, including investigation of potential violations thereof, (c) protect against harm to the rights, property or safety of Hyperboards, its users, or the public as required or permitted by law. Additionally, in the event of a reorganization, merger, or sale we may transfer any and all personal information we collect to the relevant third party.

## Your choices

After you register, you can choose to opt-out of receiving our email newsletter. However, we reserve the right to communicate with you on matters we consider especially important or relevant to material you have requested.

You can use your user dashboard to review and update the information stored in your user account.

Cookies can be disabled and managed within your browser settings. However, some features and services may not function properly with cookies disabled.

## Security

We take appropriate security measures to protect against unauthorized access, use, modification, disclosure, or destruction of your personal information. Your personal information is stored utilizing appropriate encryption on servers with firewalls and other unauthorized access prevention technologies, and is physically located in a secure facility.

Access to personal information is restricted to Hyperboards employees, staff, and agents who need to know that information to process it on our behalf.

## Publicly posted information

You may share information with other users throughout our site through various means, such as user profiles, forum posts, and personal messages. Anything you post is publicly available. Hyperboards does not control, and is not responsible for the use of any information or content that you have exposed to the public through your use of Hyperboards. Please use discretion when sharing personal information.

## Updates of this Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy is due to change from time to time. Such changes will be posted to this page and will be effective on the date thereof, and your continued use of our site will signify your acceptance of its terms.
